export const jsQuizz = {
  questions: [
    {
      question: "Which is not a feature of OOP in general definitions?",
      choices: [
        "Efficient Code",
        "Code reusability",
        "Modularity",
        "Duplicate/Redundant data",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "Duplicate/Redundant data",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which was the first purely object oriented programming language developed?",
      choices: ["Kotlin", "SmallTalk", "Java", "C++"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "SmallTalk",
    },
    {
      question: "When OOP concept did first came into picture?",
      choices: ["1980’s", "1995", "1970’s", "1993"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "1970’s",
    },
    {
      question: "Which feature of OOP indicates code reusability?",
      choices: ["Abstraction", "Polymorphism", "Encapsulation", "Inheritance"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "Inheritance",
    },
    {
      question: "Which header file is required in C++ to use OOP?",
      choices: [
        "OOP can be used without using any header file",
        "stdlib.h",
        "iostream.h",
        "stdio.h",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "OOP can be used without using any header file",
    },
    {
      question: "Why Java is Partially OOP language?",
      choices: [
        "It allows code to be written outside classes",
        "It supports usual declaration of primitive data types",
        "It does not support pointers",
        "It doesn’t support all types of inheritance",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "It supports usual declaration of primitive data types",
    },
    {
      question: "Which among the following doesn’t come under OOP concept?",
      choices: [
        "Data hiding",
        "Message passing",
        "Platform independent",
        "Data binding",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "Platform independent",
    },
    {
      question: "Which is the correct syntax of inheritance?",
      choices: [
        "class base_classname :access derived_classname{ /*define class body*/ };",
        "class derived_classname : access base_classname{ /*define class body*/ };",
        "class derived_classname : base_classname{ /*define class body*/ };",
        "class base_classname : derived_classname{ /*define class body*/ };",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer:
        "class derived_classname : access base_classname{ /*define class body*/ };",
    },
    {
      question:
        "The feature by which one object can interact with another object is _____________",
      choices: [
        "Message reading",
        "Message Passing",
        "Data transfer",
        "Data Binding",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "Message Passing",
    },
    {
      question: "Which among the following, for a pure OOP language, is true?",
      choices: [
        "The language should follow at least 1 feature of OOP",
        "The language must follow only 3 features of OOP",
        "The language must follow all the rules of OOP",
        "The language should follow 3 or more features of OOP",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "The language must follow all the rules of OOP",
    },
    {
      question: "Who developed object-oriented programming?",
      choices: ["Adele Goldberg", "Dennis Ritchie", "Alan Kay", "Andrea Ferro"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "Alan Kay",
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following is not an OOPS concept?",
      choices: ["Encapsulation", "Polymorphism", "Exception", "Abstraction"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "Exception",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which of the following language supports polymorphism but not the classes?",
      choices: [
        "C++ programming language",
        "Java programming language",
        "Ada programming language",
        "C# programming language",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "Ada programming language",
    },
    {
      question: "A single program of OOPS contains _______ classes?",
      choices: ["Only 1", "Only 999", "Only 100", "Any number"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "Any number",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which operator from the following can be used to illustrate the feature of polymorphism?",
      choices: [
        "Overloading <<",
        "Overloading &&",
        "Overloading | |",
        "Overloading +=",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "Overloading <<",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which two features of object-oriented programming are the same?",
      choices: [
        "Abstraction and Polymorphism features are the same",
        "Inheritance and Encapsulation features are the same",
        "Encapsulation and Polymorphism features are the same",
        "Encapsulation and Abstraction",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "Encapsulation and Abstraction",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which of the following definition is incorrect for polymorphism?",
      choices: [
        "Polymorphism helps in redefining the same functionality",
        "Polymorphism concept is the feature of object-oriented programming (OOP)",
        "It always increases the overhead of function definition",
        "Ease in the readability of the program",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "It always increases the overhead of function definition",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which among the following cannot be used for the concept of polymorphism?",
      choices: [
        "Static member function",
        "Constructor Overloading",
        "Member function overloading",
        "Global member function",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "Static member function",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which function best describe the concept of polymorphism in programming languages?",
      choices: [
        "Class member function",
        "Virtual function",
        "Inline function",
        "Undefined function",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "Virtual function",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which member function is assumed to call first when there is a case of using function overloading or abstract class?",
      choices: [
        "Global function",
        "Local function",
        "Function with lowest priority",
        "Function with the highest priority",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "Function with the highest priority",
    },
    {
      question: "Is it true to use polymorphism in the C programming language?",
      choices: ["True", "False"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "True",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which of the following language uses the classes but not the polymorphism concept?",
      choices: [
        "Procedure Oriented language",
        "Object-based language",
        "Class-based language",
        "If classes are used, then the polymorphism concept will always be used in the programming languages.",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "Object-based language",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which of the following OOP concept is not true for the C++ programming language?",
      choices: [
        "A class must have member functions",
        "C++ Program can be easily written without the use of classes",
        "At least one instance should be declared within the C++ program",
        "C++ Program must contain at least one class",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "C++ Program must contain at least one class",
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the extra feature in classes which was not in the structures?",
      choices: [
        "Member functions",
        "Data members",
        "Public access specifier",
        "Static Data allowed",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "Member functions",
    },
    {
      question:
        "How many types of polymorphism in the C++ programming language?",
      choices: [
        "Three types of polymorphism",
        "Two types of polymorphism",
        "Five types of polymorphism",
        "Four types of polymorphism",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "Two types of polymorphism",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which of the following feature is also known as run-time binding or late binding?",
      choices: [
        "Dynamic typing",
        "Dynamic loading",
        "Dynamic binding",
        "Data hiding",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "Dynamic binding",
    },
    {
      question: "Which among the following is not a member of the class?",
      choices: [
        "Virtual function",
        "const function",
        "Static function",
        "Friend function",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "Friend function",
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following class is known as the generic class?",
      choices: [
        "Final class",
        "Template class",
        "Abstract class",
        "Efficient code",
      ],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "Template class",
    },
    {
      question: "Which operator overloads using the friend function?",
      choices: ["*", "( )", "->", "="],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "*",
    },
    {
      question: "Write a function to reverse a string in JavaScript.",
      type: "Coding",
      correctAnswer: null,
    },
  ],
};

export const resultInitialState = {
  score: 0,
  correctAnswers: 0,
  wrongAnswers: 0,
};
